What was the biggest risk that you ever
took and how important has risk been to you?
That's a good story.
I had a newborn on the way and had
gotten down to probably the last, I think, $1,000
in my bank account or my wife's bank account.
And I decided to quit and started writing
my first product and got down to the last
$1,000 into my bank account and went and sold
the one asset I had at the time, which is
a motorcycle.
And that got us through another month or two.
Then I eventually became my business partner and he
came on board and put some of his personal
money in.
And the two of us together went
on to make a very successful company.
But to say that I put it
all on the line is not an understatement.